export default [
  {
    question: "What year was the very first model of the iPhone released?",
    answer: 2007,
    choices: [2001, 2009, 2011, 2007],
  },
  {
    question: "What’s the shortcut for the “copy” function on most computers?",
    answer: "ctrl c",
    choices: ["ctrl c", "alt tab", "ctrl v", "shift 1"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is often seen as the smallest unit of memory?",
    answer: "kilobyte",
    choices: ["megabyte", "terabyte", "kilobyte", "gigabyte"],
  },
  {
    question: "Java is a type of OS",
    answer: "false",
    choices: ["false", "true"],
  },
  {
    question: "“HTTP” stand for HyperText Transfer Prototype",
    answer: "false",
    choices: ["false", "true"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the man who launched eBay back in 1995?",
    answer: "Pierre Omidyar",
    choices: ["Corvus Glaive", "Ebony Maw", "Pierre Omidyar", "Cull Obsidian"],
  },
  {
    question: "Hotmail is owned by Microsoft?",
    answer: "true",
    choices: ["false", "true"],
  },
  {
    question: "Google Chrome, and Explorer are different types of what?",
    answer: "Web browsers",
    choices: ["software", "search engine", "Web browsers", "none of the above"],
  },
  {
    question: "Twitter’s original name is twttr",
    answer: "true",
    choices: ["true", "false"],
  },
  {
    question: "CSS stands for Cascading Style Sheets",
    answer: "true",
    choices: ["true", "false"],
  },
];

export const source = "https://www.opinionstage.com/blog/trivia-questions/";
